Guide to the Julius Bernstein Papers WAG.116
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Subject Files, 1920-1984
  - JLC: Boston Newsletter, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Labor Committee California, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - JLC: Child Adoption Program, 1948-1953 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - JLC: Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - JLC: Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - JLC: Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - JLC: Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - JLC Conference, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - JLC Conference, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - JLC Conference, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1950 I (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1950 II (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - JLC Correspondence, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - JLC: Educators' Chapter, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - JLC: Federations, 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - JLC: Federations, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - JLC: Federations, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - JLC: Federations, 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - JLC: Federations, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - JLC: Federations, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - JLC: Federations, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - JLC: Federations, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - JLC: Field Reports, Jan 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - JLC: Field Reports, Jul 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - JLC: Field Reports, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - JLC: Framingham Outings, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - JLC: Fund Raising, 1955-1961 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Labor Committee Institute, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - JLC: Institute on Jewish Affairs, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - JLC: Labor and Civil Rights, 1955-1959 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - JLC: Labor and Civil Rights, 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - JLC: Los Angeles, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - JLC: Luncheons, 1954-1961 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - JLC: Minutes and Contact Sheets, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - JLC: Monthly Reports, 1949-1953 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - JLC: Monthly Reports, 1955-1960 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - JLC: Monthly Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - JLC: Monthly Reports, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - JLC: Monthly Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - JLC: Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - JLC: New Bedford, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - JLC: Regional Conferences, 1955-1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - JLC: 25th Anniversary, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - JLC: Welfare Fund Committee, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - JLC: Women's Division, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Population Shifts, 1950-1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Professionals, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Socialist Youth Bund, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10a)
  - Jewish Society of Americanists, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Vote, 1956-1964 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Jewish War Veterans, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Civil Rights, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Job Creation: Massachusetts, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 14a)
  - Job Discrimination and Jewish Youth, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Job Satisfaction, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - John Birch Society, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - John Birch Society, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - John Birch Society, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - John Birch Society, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - John Birch Society, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - John Birch Society, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - John Birch Society, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - John Birch Society, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - John Birch Society, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - John Birch Society: Communist Merchandise Boycott, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - John Birch Society: George Wallace, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - John Birch Society and Metco, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - John Birch Society and the Police, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Jordan: Arms Sale, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Kahane, Mier, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 30a)
  - Kamp, Joseph R., 1955-1958 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Kelmsley, Bill, 1956, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Kerner Commission, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 32a)
  - King, Dr. Martin Luther, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - King, Melvin M., 1967-1973 (Box 17, Folder 33a)
  - Kleinman, Rose Parker, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 33b)
  - Kregeloh, Hubert, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Kuchel Case, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1952-1967 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Labor and Civil Liberties, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Labor and Civil Rights, 1947-1955 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Labor and Civil Rights, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Labor and Civil Rights, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Labor and Civil Rights, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Labor and Civil Rights, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Labor and Civil Rights: Schools, 1963-1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Labor Educational Association, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Labor Committee for Human Rights, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Labor Discussion Group, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Labor Discussion Group, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Labor Education Council, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10a)
  - Labor: General, 1948-1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Labor Guild: Archdiocese of Boston, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 11a)
  - Labor History, 1927-1951 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Labor Institute, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 12a)
  - Labor Institute on Civil Rights, 1950-1957 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Labor Institute for Human Relations, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Labor Institute for Human Relations, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Labor Institute for Human Rights, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Labor Institute for Human Rights, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Labor: Massachusetts, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Labor Legislation: Landrum-Griffin Bill, 1951-1959 (Box 18, Folder 18a)
  - Labor Legislation: Massachusetts Referendum, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 18b)
  - Labor-Student Alliance, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Labor University Group, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lapan, Martin, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20a)
  - Larouche, Lyndon, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Lawrence, Massachusetts: Jewish Community Council, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 22a)
  - Leafer, Ray: Discrimination Case, 1953-1954, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1965, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1954-1971 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: State, 1955-1967 (Box 18, Folder 25a)
  - Let Freedom Ring, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1963-1966, undated (Box 18, Folder 26a)
  - Liberal Citizens of Massachusetts, 1954-1962 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Liberty Amendment Committee, 1961-1967 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Liberty House of Cambridge, MA, Harvey Cox, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 28a)
  - Liberty Letter, 1967-1971 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Liberty Lobby, 1961-1971 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Lie Detector, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Life-Line Foundation (H.L. Hunt), 1954-1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Longshoremen, 1951, 1961-1963 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Lovestone, Jay, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Low Income Planning Aid, (1974)? (Box 18, Folder 34a)
  - Loyalty Oaths, 1961-1962, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Macner Report, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Maine, 1954-1977 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Maine: Ben Dorsky, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Maine: Bureau of Labor Education, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Maine: Equal Opportunities Bill, 1958-1959, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Maine State Federation of Labor, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Manion Forum, 1958-1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Mantle Club, 1950-1961 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Maoists, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - March on Boston, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - March on Washington, DC, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Markey, Edward, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Marshall, Ray, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts AFL-CIO, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts AFL-CIO: Civil Rights Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts AFL-CIO Newsletter, 1972-1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Committee on Civil Rights, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Committee on Civil Rights, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Citizens League for Political Education, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Coalition for Full Employment, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts Coalition for Human Rights, 1952-1966, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts Coalition for Human Rights, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Coalition for Human Rights, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts Coalition for Occupational Safety and Health (MASSCOSH), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination I, 1952-1964 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination II, 1952-1964 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination I, 1970-1977 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination II, 1970-1977 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Apprentice Training Study, 1952-1962 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Cases, 1952-1976 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Evaluations, 1950s-1960s (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Evaluations, 1960s-1976 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Fair Educational Practices, 1953-1966 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination: Federal Block Grants Protest, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Housing, 1957-1960 (Box 19A, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Commission against Discrimination: Transportation Industry Report, 1966 (Box 19A, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Commission of Catholics, Protestants, and Jews, 1955-1961 (Box 19A, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Commission on Human Rights: Report on Boston, 1975 (Box 19A, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Committee for Fair Housing Practices, 1950-1960 (Box 19A, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Committee on Constitutional Rights, 1966-1970 (Box 19A, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1962-1963 (Box 19A, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1964-1965 (Box 19A, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1966-1968 (Box 19A, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Community Center, 1974 (Box 19A, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Conference on Children and Youth, 1964 (Box 19A, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Conference on Human Rights, 1969-1970 (Box 19A, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Council for Civil Rights, 1952-1954 (Box 19A, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Council for Civil Rights, 1958-1964 (Box 19A, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Council for Constitutional Rights, 1953 (Box 19A, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Council for Constitutional Rights, 1966 (Box 19A, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts Council for Public Schools, 1958 (Box 19A, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts Council for Public Schools, 1966-1969 (Box 19A, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Federation of Labor, 1953-1958 (Box 19A, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts Freedom Movement, undated (Box 19A, Folder 21)
  - Massachusetts Full Employment Council, 1977 (Box 19A, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts Labor Committee of Human Rights, 1957-1966 (Box 19A, Folder 23)
  - Massachusetts Political Action for Peace, 1962-1964 (Box 19A, Folder 24)
  - Massachusetts Political Action for Peace, 1965-1966 (Box 19A, Folder 25)
  - Massachusetts Rehabilitation Hospital: Strike, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Social and Economic Opportunity Council, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts State Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts State CIO, 1953-1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts State Equal Rights Amendment, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts State Industrial Union Council, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts State Labor Council, 1958-1962, 1967-1968, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts State Labor Council: Resolutions, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts. Task Force on Affirmative Action in Education, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Tomorrow, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Tomorrow: Conference, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Union of Public Housing Tenants, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Mattapan, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Mattapan-Dorchester Service Center, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Mattapan Jewish Community Center, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Mattapan Project, 1967-1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Mayor's Human Relations Task Force (Boston): Conference, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Mayor's Office of Human Rights, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - May 2nd Movement, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - McCarthy and Dissenting Democrats, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - McCarthyism: CIO, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - McCarthyism: Massachusetts Response, 1952-1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Medicare/Medicaid, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Mental Health, 1954-1964 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Mexican-Americans: Support for Israel, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Middle East, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Middle East, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Middle East, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Middle East and Labor, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Middle East and Israel, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Middle East: CJP-JCC Joint Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Middle East: CJP-JCC Joint Committee, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Middle East Rally (Boston), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Migrant Education Program, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Military "Muzzling" Hearings, 1962 (Box 21, Folder a)
  - Milton, Massachusetts, 1955 (Box 21, Folder b)
  - Minimum Wage, 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder c)
  - Minutemen, 1961-1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Mobilizations, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Moratorium Committee, Cambridge, MA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3a)
  - Movement for Economic Justice, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Multi-Nationalists, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Muste Dinner, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Whiteys, 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - National Committee for Full Employment, undated (Box 21, Folder 9a)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1950-1960 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - National Council against Conscription, 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - National Council against Conscription, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - National Council for Civil Responsibility, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - National Education Program (Right Wing Films), 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - National Executive Committee: Minutes, 1953, 1957-1959, 1961-1971 (Box 21, Folder 14a)
  - National Health Service (Britain), 1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), 1944-1954 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - NCRAC, 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - NCRAC, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - NCRAC: Civil Liberties, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - NCRAC: Employment, 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - NCRAC: Executive Committee Meetings, 1953-1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - NCRAC: Massachusetts, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - NCRAC: Veterans, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - National Organization for Women, California, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 25a)
  - National Renaissance Party- James H. Madole, 1961-1966 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - National State's Rights Party, 1961-1966, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - National Trade Union Council for Human Rights (NTUC), undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - NTUC: 1st Conference, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - NTUC: 2nd Conference, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - NTUC: 4th Conference, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - NTUC: 5th Conference, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - National Economic Council, 1948-1967 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Nationalist Party, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Negro History, 1962-1969 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Newark, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - New Bedford, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - New Bedford: Police, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - New Careers, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - New England Conference on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 39a)
  - New England Rally for God, Family, and Country, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 39b)
  - New Hampshire, 1954-1957 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - New Hampshire, 1958-1965, 1969, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - New Hampshire: Anti-Discrimination Bill, 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - New Hampshire: Anti-Discrimination Law, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - New Hampshire: Labor, Civil Rights, Etc., 1952 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - New Hampshire: Labor, Civil Rights, Etc., 1953 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - New Hampshire: Labor, Civil Rights, Etc., 1954-1966 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - New Hampshire: Labor, Civil Rights Clippings, 1952-1963 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - New Hampshire State Labor Council: Resolutions, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 47a)
  - New Jersey, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - New Left, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - New Left: Students, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - New Party News, 1945-1947 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - New Political Party, 1939-1946 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - New School/Free University Project, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - New York City Review Board Conference, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Newton Group, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - 1976 Committee (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Nixon and Civil Rights, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - None Dare Call It Treason, undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - North American Jewish Student Network, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - North Carolina: Textile Workers, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - North of Boston, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Nursing: Discrimination, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Ohio AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Olympics, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Organization of African-American Veterans, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 3a)
  - Ostrow, Alice, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3b)
  - Ostrow, Pierson, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3c)
  - Painters District Council, #35, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Passports, 1955-1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Peace Movement, 1938, 1959, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - People's Platform, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - People's Platform: Newsletter, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia Jewish Labor Committee: University of Pennsylvania Protest, undated (Box 22, Folder 7a)
  - Pillion, John R. Resolution, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, undated (Box 22, Folder 8a)
  - Policastro, Thomas, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8b)
  - Police, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Police: Boston, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Police: Boston, Commissioner Robert di Grazia, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Police Brutality, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Polish Anti-Semitism, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Polish Jewry, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Political Informers: Petition Against, undated (Box 22, Folder 14a)
  - Pollution, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Poor People's Campaign, undated (Box 22, Folder 15a)
  - Post-War World Council (Norman Thomas), 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 15b)
  - Poverty, 1961-1967, 1970, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Poverty: Citizen's Crusade Against, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Poverty in Massachusetts, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Poverty Program, 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Poverty Program, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Poverty Program: OEO, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Poverty: Youth, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 22a)
  - Prague Purge Trials, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 22b)
  - Prayer Amendment, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Presidential Candidates on Massachusetts Ballot, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Press: Eastland Investigation, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Prison Reform, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Progressive Labor Boston, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1963-1967 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Project Equality, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 31a)
  - Propaganda, 1952, 1960-1966 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Protest Rally versus Soviet Policy in Hungary and Egypt, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 32a)
  - Protestant-Jewish Dialogue, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Protestant War Veterans Legion, 1955-1960 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Providence, RI: Jewish Federation Allocation, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 34a)
  - Public Affairs Issues: Human Relations, Civil Rights, Labor, etc., 1940-1950 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Public Employee Rights, 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Public Service Employment, 1971-1976 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Puerto Ricans, 1952-1969 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Puerto Ricans: Boston and Springfield, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Puerto Ricans in Boston, 1964-1973 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Quality of Working Life (QWL), 1970 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Quality of Working Life, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Quinn, Robert, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Raby, Al: Boston Talk, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Race and Ability, 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Race Relations: Boston, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Racial Imbalance Law, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Railway Unions, 1952-1961 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Randolph, Philip A., 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Rat Finks (NJ), 1967-1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Religion and Labor, 1946-1950 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Religion and Race, 1957-1964 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Religion in Schools: Becker Amendment, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Religion in Schools: Clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Religion in Schools: Community Tensions, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Religion in Schools: General, 1940-1949 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Religion in Schools: General, 1950-1954 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Religion in Schools: General, 1955-1959 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Religion in Schools: General, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Religion in Schools: General, 1970-1979 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Religion in Schools: Holidays, 1955-1963 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Religion in Schools: Massachusetts, 1947, 1950-1959 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Religion in Schools: Massachusetts, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Religion in Schools: Prayer Decision, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Religion in Schools: Prayer Decision: Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)